<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<mydata>
  <row>
    <content>While the bulk of the analysis is complete, Stuxnet is an incredibly large and complex threat. 
The authors expect to make revisions to this document shortly after release as new 
information is uncovered or may be publicly disclosed. This paper is the work of numerous ...</content>
    <author>N Falliere, LO Murchu, E Chien - White paper, Symantec Corp., …, 2011 - ants.mju.ac.kr</author>
    <title>[PDF] W32. stuxnet dossier</title>
  </row>
  <row>
    <content>completely new approach that's no longer aligned with conventional confidentiality, integrity, 
and availability thinking. Contrary to initial belief, Stuxnet wasn't about industrial espionage: 
it didn't steal, manipulate, or erase information. Rather, Stuxnet's goal was to physically ...</content>
    <author>R Langner - Security & Privacy, IEEE, 2011 - ieeexplore.ieee.org</author>
    <title>Stuxnet: Dissecting a cyberwarfare weapon</title>
  </row>
  <row>
    <content>Thousands of new mal-ware appear in the wild daily. Most are evolutionary variants of 
existing families and don't have a widespread impact. However, occasionally a noteworthy 
new piece of malware will change the security landscape. For example, the 1988 Morris ...</content>
    <author>TM Chen, S Abu-Nimeh - Computer, 2011 - ieeexplore.ieee.org</author>
    <title>Lessons from stuxnet</title>
  </row>
  <row>
    <content>The discovery in June 2010 that a cyber worm dubbed 'Stuxnet'had struck the Iranian 
nuclear facility at Natanz suggested that, for cyber war, the future is now. Yet more important 
is the political and strategic context in which new cyber threats are emerging, and the ...</content>
    <author>JP Farwell, R Rohozinski - Survival, 2011 - Taylor & Francis</author>
    <title>Stuxnet and the future of cyber war</title>
  </row>
  <row>
    <content>In recent years, the press has been banging the drums about the prospects of cyber warfare 
between nations. It makes a good story. In the imagined scenario, national governments are 
gathering and training elite teams of computer hackers prepared to infiltrate or take down ...</content>
    <author>TM Chen - Network, IEEE, 2010 - ieeexplore.ieee.org</author>
    <title>Stuxnet, the real start of cyber warfare?[Editor's Note]</title>
  </row>
  <row>
    <content>This report is devoted to the analysis of the notorious Stuxnet worm (Win32/Stuxnet) that 
suddenly attracted the attention of virus researchers this summer. This report is primarily 
intended to describe targeted and semi-targeted attacks, and how they are implemented, ...</content>
    <author>D Albright, P Brannan, C Walrond - 2010 - Institute for Science and …</author>
    <title>[CITATION] Did Stuxnet Take Out 1,000 Centrifuges at the Natanz Enrichment Plant?</title>
  </row>
</mydata>
